shopathome.com 2013-05-31

# Privacy Policy - ShopAtHome.com

Effective Date: December 1, 2011

This Privacy Policy applies to www.shopathome.com (the "Site") and the ShopAtHome.com Shopping Toolbar ("[Shopping Toolbar](http://www.shopathome.com/terms-and-conditions.aspx?#ShoppingToolbar)"). At ShopAtHome.com we recognize and respect your privacy This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and disclose personally identifying information ("Personal Information") gathered through our Site and Shopping Toolbar. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy. By using the Site or our Shopping Toolbar, you agree that you have read, understand and agree to this Privacy Policy, which incorporates by reference our Terms and Conditions, including their limitation on liability. To review our Terms and Conditions, click [here](http://www.shopathome.com/terms-and-conditions.aspx)

TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
You may browse our Site without registering, but to use certain features, such as our Shopping Toolbar, and to participate in the Cash Back Rewards program, you must register with us. We may collect information directly from you, from your use of the Site and Shopping Toolbar, and from other sources. In general, we collect the following types of information from users:

  * Account and Registration Information. When you register with us, we collect your email address, zip code, and a password (that you will use to log in). We may also ask you for profile and demographic information (such as name, gender, phone number, address, and date of birth), and information about your preferences (such as your favorite stores).

  * Purchases. When you make a purchase from an [Affiliate Store](http://www.shopathome.com/terms-and-conditions.aspx?#AffiliateStores), we receive information about your purchase, including the products purchased and the date and amount of the purchase, as explained more fully in the "Affiliate Stores and Affiliate Networks" section below.

  * Payment Information. For some transactions, we may collect payment information from you, including your credit or debit card number, billing address and other information necessary to process your transaction. While we retain your billing address as part of your account profile, we will not store your credit card information for future use unless you tell us to remember it.

  * Shopping Toolbar History. If you have elected to download our Shopping Toolbar, we collect information about your browsing and searching history. For more information, see the "Shopping Toolbar" section below.

  * Interaction with Third Party Sites. You can use features such as the Site's Facebook Connect feature to connect your social media sites to ShopAtHome.com and share information about us. If you use a social media site in connection with the Site, we may collect your user name and other profile information. For more information see the "Social Media Users" section below

  * Other Information. We may collect other information about you that you enter on our Site. For example, if you post content to the Site, we collect information about that content. If you refer a friend to ShopAtHome.com, we collect information about that referral, including the friend's e-mail address.

  * Information We Automatically Collect. We automatically collect through our Sites and Shopping Toolbar certain information, including IP address, the website from which visitors came to our Site, browser type, clickstream data, and other information relating to the device through which you access the Site or use the Shopping Toolbar. We may combine the information we collect from you automatically with the other information we collect about you.

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION.  
In general, we use the Personal Information we collect from you for the following purposes:

  * To process and fulfill your orders and for other customer-service-related purposes

  * To administer our Cash Back Rewards Program and to process your Cash Back Rewards

  * To communicate with you about your account or about your order

  * To send you marketing and promotional e-mails (unless you have opted out)

  * To display targeted advertisements, customized search results, and other customized content and offers to you based upon your location and your shopping, browsing and/or searching history

  * To redirect you through the ShopAtHome.com network so that you may take advantage of our rewards and offers

  * To better understand how users access and use our Site and Shopping Toolbar

  * To improve the design of our Site and Shopping Toolbar, and our other products and services

  * To analyze user trends, including browsing, shopping and searching trends 

  * To protect the security or integrity of the Site, Shopping Toolbar and our business

  * To investigate, prevent or take action regarding violations of this Privacy Policy or the Terms and Conditions

In addition, we may freely use aggregate, de-identified or otherwise non-personally identifying information about users for marketing, advertising, research or other purposes.

HOW WE DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION   
We may disclose the Personal Information we collect from you to third parties for the following purposes:

  * To our contractors or service providers who provide services or perform functions on our behalf, such as those that we employ to remove duplicate information from customer lists, provide database analysis, serve customer content or perform site analytics.

  * To an Affiliate Store when needed to fulfill your request or order for products or services from that Affiliate Store. 

  * In response to a subpoena or other legal process, or if otherwise required by law; 

  * To protect or enforce our rights or property, this Privacy Policy or our Terms and Conditions; or

  * In the event of the sale or dissolution (bankruptcy) of assets of part or of all of our business or any of its affiliates.

  * We may also freely share and disclose aggregate, de-identified or otherwise non-personally identifying information about users with third parties for marketing, advertising, research or other purposes. For example, if we display advertisements on behalf of a third party, we may share aggregate, demographic information with that third party about the users to whom we displayed the advertisements. 

COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES  
When you interact with our Site or use our Shopping Toolbar, we strive to make your experience easy and meaningful. We or our third party service providers may use cookies, web beacons (clear GIFs, web bugs) and other technologies to track user activity and collect Site data. We may combine this information with the Personal Information we have collected about you

Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to track information about your activities on the ShopAtHome.com site, your use of our Shopping Toolbar, your visit to a ShopAtHome.com merchant, and information about when a ShopAtHome.com merchant appears in your search results. We also use cookies to store your preferences and to allow you to remain logged in as you use our Site.

Disabling Cookies. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. If you disable cookies, you may still browse our Site, but you many of our features will not work, including the Shopping Toolbar, and you will not be able to participate in the Cash Back Rewards program.

Web Beacons (Clear Gifs/Web Bugs). We or the third parties we employ may use web beacons (a.k.a. Clear Gifs/Web Bugs) on our Site to help us better manage content on the Site. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer's hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on webpages. We may also use web beacons in our HTML-based emails, to let us know which emails have been opened or forwarded by recipients. 

Third Party Service Providers. As noted above, we may employ third-party service providers to perform site functions for us, such as serving customer content, collecting IP address, location information and anonymous traffic data, or performing site analytics. These vendors may place and read cookies or web beacons on your browser to perform these functions. They have access to the user information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

Affiliate Stores. Other third-party entities, such as Affiliate Stores and the affiliate networks in which they participate, may also place cookies to track transactions and credit ShopAtHome.com for referrals made through ShopAtHome.com. Such third parties use of cookies is subject to their respective privacy policies, not this one. See "Affiliate Stores and Networks" below.

Third-Party Advertisements. In addition, we may participate in third party ad network and make available to our Site users specific offers from third-party companies. These companies and ad networks may utilize cookies and web beacons in connection with the delivery of their offers and to serve ads based on your use of our Site or other internet sites. Their use of cookies and other tracking technologies is subject to their respective privacy policies, not this one. However, we will not share your Personal Information with these third parties.

Opting Out of Third-Party Ad Networks. If you wish to opt-out of receiving cookies from certain third party ad networks, you may do so through the Network Advertising Initiative cookie opt-out page, which can be found at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. You may also visit [www.AboutAds.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to learn more about online advertising, and to opt-out of certain online behavioral advertising activities. ShopAtHome.com adheres to the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. 

SHOPPING TOOLBAR  
As noted above, we collect information about the searching and browsing history of users of our Shopping Toolbar. We use this information to redirect you through the ShopAtHome.com network, as well as for other purposes as stated in the "How We Use Your Information" section, above. We may also display directly in your search engine search results, relevant and customized content, results and advertising, and may highlight or identify ShopAtHome.com merchants that appear in your results, so that you may continue to take full advantage of the ShopAtHome.com network, even when you are not searching directly on the ShopAtHome.com site. In order to do this, our Shopping Toolbar gathers data about your searches and browsing activities – we combine and compare this information with the other information we collect and maintain about you. If you do not wish ShopAtHome.com to continue to collect this information about your browsing and search history, you must uninstall the Shopping Toolbar. 

USER CONTENT  
We may allow users to post information, such as blogs and comments, to our Sites. Any information that you post to our Sites becomes public information and may be viewable by any visitors to our Site. We cannot prevent the content you post from being used by others in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy, the law, or your personal privacy. Your posting of any content to our Site is at your own discretion and is subject to our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.shopathome.com/terms-and-conditions.aspx). 

SOCIAL MEDIA USERS  
As noted above, you can utilize functions such as Facebook Connect to share information about us, invite your contacts to use the Site, and share content you post on the Site. To use these functions, you must enter your third party site credentials and grant ShopAtHome.com permission to access and collect your basic social networking site information (which generally includes your name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, and any other information you've shared with everyone). If you tell your social media contacts about us, we will see and may store that contact's user ID. If you choose to link your social media profile to the Site (for example, by "Liking" ShopAtHome.com), we receive information which may include your user ID, the pages you were visiting when you chose to link to us or otherwise bring us to the attention of your contacts, and other information about offers in which you are interested. We may also collect any profile information that you share with everyone. For some social media sites, such as LinkedIn, if you agree on the social media site to share your data with third parties, we may collect your data from the social media site. To review and manage the privacy settings for your social media account, including the information you share with everyone, you should refer to the privacy settings for your social media account and that website's privacy policy – we have no control over what profile information is shared or made public by other sites. 

THIRD-PARTY LINKS  
Third party companies show our ads on various sites on the internet. Our Site may also contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such third-party sites or companies. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy policies of any other site that collects Personal information. 

MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS  
We may send you newsletters, as well as emails about information that we (or third parties) believe may be of interest to you, including offers from us or other third parties. Upon enrollment, ShopAtHome.com members may opt-out of receiving these newsletters and promotional e-mails. However, we announce our latest deals and special offers in these emails, sometimes before they are posted on the Site – thus by opting out you may not receive information about all of these promotions. 

If, at any time, you would like to stop receiving these promotional e-mails, please follow the opt-out instructions contained in any such e-mail, or may manage your e-mail preferences by logging in to your Account and updating your "Account Preferences." Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out requests. If you opt-out of receiving promotional emails from us, we may continue to send you e-mails about your account, any services that you have requested or received from us or for other customer services purposes. 

AFFILIATE STORES AND AFFILIATE NETWORKS  
We and our Affiliate Stores participate in certain affiliate marketing networks, otherwise known as affiliate networks. An affiliate network acts as an intermediary between ShopAtHome.com and our Affiliate Stores (merchants or retailers). By participating in an affiliate network, ShopAtHome.com can make cash-back rewards, offers and deals related to participating Affiliate Stores available to ShopAtHome.com users. 

The affiliate networks we participate in and our Affiliate Stores may share with us data about you and your purchases with Affiliate Stores, which may include the amount of your order, your e-mail address, the time and date of the transaction, the order number, the product(s) purchased, and a unique customer ID. This information allows us to properly assign you Cash Back Reward credits. For information about the privacy practices of these Affiliate Stores and ad networks, you should consult their respective privacy policies. We do not have any control over how these Affiliate Stores or affiliate networks treat the Personal Information they collect from you. We are not responsible for the actions or policies of any Affiliate Store sites, including web pages from an Affiliate Store's site that are "framed" within the ShopAtHome.com Site. 

HOW TO UPDATE YOUR INFORMATION  
ou may change the information we have on file for you at any time by simply clicking on the "My Account" link under the Community tab at the top of the page when you are logged in, or by clicking [here](http://www.shopathome.com/MyAccount.aspx), and making your desired changes. Please allow up to 10 business days to process account changes. 

SECURITY  
We use reasonable physical, technical and administrative measures to protect the security of the Personal Information that you provide to us. For example, ShopAtHome.com utilizes, where appropriate, firewall and Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. Despite our efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security all of the time. 

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY  
ShopAtHome.com has the right to change this policy, without prior notification to you. If we do so, we will change the effective date above. We encourage you to review this privacy policy from time to time. If we materially change our practices with regard to Personal Information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice, such as, where appropriate, email notice or notice posted at our Site. 

CONTACT US  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our practices, you may contact us at: 

ShopAtHome.com  
Attn: Privacy  
7100 East Belleview Avenue, #208  
Greenwood Village, CO 80111  
Email: privacy@shopathome.com
